hi sporting fans welcome to another
嗨，体育迷们欢迎来到另一个
installment of spring tips in which
在其中安装的Spring 头
we're going to look at kafka streams in
我们将在
particular we're going to look at kafka
特别是我们要看一下卡夫卡
streams through the lens of spring cloud
穿过Spring Cloud的镜头
stream now in a previous video we looked
现在我们在上一个视频中观看了
at a spring cloud stream and everyday we
在 Spring 的云流中，我们每天
looked at sprinkled stream and RabbitMQ
看着洒水和RabbitMQ
now broadly sprinkled stream is a
现在散落的溪流是
framework that handles the connectivity
处理连通性的框架
of different messaging technologies and
不同的消息传递技术和
allows us to write code in terms of
允许我们按照以下方式编写代码
these sort of useful programming api's
这类有用的编程API
and the default sort of approach is to
默认的方法是
use the Spring Framework messaging
使用Spring Framework消息传递
channel and messaging you know message
您知道消息的频道和消息
type so those types are the core of the
类型，所以这些类型是
of spring cloud stream but that's no
Spring 的云流，但那不是
reason there's no reason you couldn't
原因是没有理由你不能
use other bindings as well so today
今天也使用其他绑定
we're gonna look at spring cloud stream
我们要看 Spring 的云流
and kafka streams it allows us to work
和卡夫卡流，它使我们能够工作
with bindings from the kafka streams
来自kafka流的绑定
project now we're gonna build a simple
现在我们要建立一个简单的项目
analytics application I'm gonna use the
分析应用程序，我将使用
Kafka support the spring Cloud stream
卡夫卡支持 Spring Cloud Stream
support Lombok and the web support this
支持龙目岛，网络对此提供支持
will give us a new project which we can
将给我们一个新项目，我们可以
open up in our on our IDE and this you
在我们的IDE上打开，然后您
know this API is gonna build a simple
知道这个API会建立一个简单的
app analytics application that's gonna
应用分析应用程序
process event coming off of let's say
流程事件说出来
some sort of imagined website or
某种想象中的网站或
something like that the data that we
像这样的数据，我们
process we're going to then to wouldn't
我们将要去的过程
need to go to to synthesize we're going
需要去综合我们要
to create some data you know as though
创建一些你知道的数据
there was a somebody actually clicking
实际上有人在点击
around in a website for example we're
例如在一个网站周围
gonna synthesize some data in order to
将合成一些数据以便
do that we're gonna use regular spring
这样做我们会定期使用 Spring
cloud stream and then and only then are
云流，然后只有那时
we gonna start to use spring cloud
我们将开始使用Spring 云
stream and kafka streams to to to
流和kafka流到
process that data to to a to work with
处理该数据到与
with that data so two binders here and
有了这些数据，所以这里有两个活页夹
the same application so spring cloud
Spring Cloud同样的应用
stream binder Kafka stream and spring
流活页夹卡夫卡流和 Spring
cloud stream Kafka ok binder Kafka so I
云流卡夫卡确定活页夹卡夫卡所以我
think that's some that's the right one
认为那是正确的
let's go ahead and make sure give it a
让我们继续并确保给它一个
second here to download
第二这里下载
so probably maybe it's s caucus streams
所以大概是核心会议
that looks like it's the right version
看起来是正确的版本
so that with that in place let's go
这样就可以开始了
ahead and build an application that
并构建一个应用程序
writes data to our Kafka broker now we
现在，我们将数据写入我们的Kafka经纪人
should talk about Kafka a little bit
应该稍微谈谈卡夫卡
here we should understand what it is
在这里我们应该了解它是什么
Kafka is a message broker from so now
Kafka从现在开始就是一个消息代理
patent it's now an Apache project it's
专利，现在是Apache项目，
very popular especially among the
非常受欢迎，尤其是在
internet darlings the web Giants for for
网络巨人的网络巨人
a number of reasons first of all it's
首先有很多原因
got a very very flexible topology or
具有非常非常灵活的拓扑或
domain model it gives you a very
域模型，它给你一个非常
flexible way to describe different
灵活的方式来描述不同
systems right it it uh it can be used to
系统吧，它可以用来
do pub/sub or qtq or point to point
做pub / sub或qtq或点对点
rather messaging but the the thing that
而不是消息传递，而是
allows allows that kind of flexibility
允许允许那种灵活性
partitions and groups is generic and so
分区和组是通用的，因此
the actually you can actually do some
实际上你可以做一些
other things besides that as well you
除此之外，你还有其他事情
can do some very interesting is you can
可以做一些非常有趣的事
actually for example have point-to-point
实际上例如具有点对点
messaging that's also got multiple
消息也很多
subscribers for example you can do you
订户，例如你可以
know you can scale up and do load
知道你可以扩大规模并做负荷
balancing with the same primitives right
用相同的原语平衡
which is not necessarily always true of
这不一定总是正确的
a other messaging systems Kafka
其他消息传递系统Kafka
ultimately when if you asks if you ask
最终当你问是否问
people who work on Kafka what it is
在卡夫卡工作的人是什么
whether they whether it's a traditional
他们是否是传统的
enterprise messaging broker or something
企业消息传递代理之类的
they're more than likely going to tell
他们更有可能讲
you that it's a replicated log right
你这是一个复制的日志
it's actually a log it's a log of of
它实际上是一个日志
records stored in a sequence and there
记录按顺序存储在那里
can be multiple messages in that
可以是多个消息
sequence of course and they're they are
当然顺序，他们是
put into a category and that category is
放入一个类别，该类别是
called the topic so whereas in JMS or
称为主题，因此在JMS或
rabbitmq or something you have top
Rabbitmq或您拥有的顶级产品
excused exchanges etc and Kafka it's all
原谅的交流等等，卡夫卡就这些
just topic and you put records into
只是主题，您将记录放入
these categories called topics these
这些类别称为主题
records are messages we can think of
记录是我们可以想到的消息
them as messages but within a topic you
它们作为消息，但在主题内
can have multiple partitions and these
可以有多个分区，这些
partitions meaning that you can actually
分区意味着您实际上可以
have you know only you know you have
你知道吗只有你知道你有
guarantees about ordering only within
保证只在内部订购
one partition the benefit of that is
一个分区的好处是
that I can have multiple consumers each
我每个人可以有多个消费者
processing a different partition but
处理不同的分区，但是
they're still working from the same
他们仍然在同一个地方工作
topic alright so there they get linear
主题很好，所以它们变得线性
linear linearizable
线性可线性化
processing that can also be done
也可以做的处理
concurrently which is very very very
同时非常非常非常
convenient very very convenient quality
方便非常非常方便的质量
also that replicated log is built in
也是内置的复制日志
such a way that it's optimized for this
对此进行了优化的方式
kind of thing it's optimized for large
专门针对大型应用进行了优化
amount of data and so really what we're
大量的数据，所以实际上我们是
dealing with here is a database that you
在这里处理的是您的数据库
can treat like a FIFO and it's a
可以像FIFO一样对待
database that has data that you can read
具有您可以读取的数据的数据库
in and out right like a like a like a
一进一出就像一个像一个像
nutritional message queue this database
营养信息将该数据库排队
I mean you know that the query time the
我的意思是你知道查询时间
constant lookup time for messages in the
消息中恒定的查询时间
database means that you can have 10
数据库意味着您可以拥有10个
kilobytes of data or you can have 10
千字节的数据，或者您可以拥有10
terabytes of data the the seek time the
TB级数据的寻道时间
the index in time for particular record
特定记录的时间索引
it's constant and that gives you some
它是不变的，这给你一些
very very very useful properties
非常非常非常有用的属性
especially at scale and especially when
尤其是大规模的时候
dealing with a constant load okay so
处理恒定的负载就可以了
we've got now there's some
我们现在有一些
simplification what we do is going to
简化我们要做的是
create a an application that writes data
创建一个写数据的应用程序
to our to our Kafka broker I have Kafka
给我们给我们的卡夫卡经纪人我有卡夫卡
running here in the background I've got
我在后台运行在这里
the zookeeper instance and then I
动物园管理员实例，然后我
started up Kafka and you can just
启动卡夫卡，你可以
download a prebuilt uh you know
下载预建的呃你知道的
distribution of cauca of Kafka from the
卡夫卡草的分布
Apache web site and just start them up
Apache网站并启动它们
okay and I've got our new application so
好，我有我们的新应用程序，所以
I'm gonna build an application that
我要建立一个应用程序
produces data so it's gonna be a write
产生数据，所以它将被写入
data of type page view right page view
类型页面视图的数据右页面视图
event or just yeah this is called page
事件或只是，这被称为页面
view event sure and the page view event
查看事件确定和页面查看事件
will contain information about who's
将包含有关谁的信息
making the request about the page that
提出有关该页面的请求
they're viewing and the duration of the
他们正在查看和持续时间
view right how long were they on a given
正确查看给定的时间
page now I'm gonna use one buck to
现在我要用一美元
create some you know detail elect things
创建一些你知道的细节选举的东西
here and we're going to create a page
在这里，我们将创建一个页面
view event source we're gonna create a
查看事件源，我们将创建一个
thing that gets called when the
当
application stood up and it's going to
应用程序站起来，它将
write data to the database when it
当数据写入数据库时
starts up its gonna have this callback
启动它将会有这个回调
that's where I data to this broker
那是我向该经纪人数据的地方
actually this Kafka broker so we're
其实这个卡夫卡经纪人，所以我们
gonna say it's a component and it in
要说这是一个组成部分
turn is going to use a regular spring
轮到要使用常规Spring
cloud stream binding so again here as
云流绑定在这里再次如此
where it pays to have pay attention to
需要注意的地方
that last video so we're just gonna
那最后一个视频，所以我们要
create an interface and define some
创建一个界面并定义一些
channels some output channels into which
引导一些输出通道，
we can send messages and the reason we
我们可以发送消息以及我们的原因
have this sort of
有这种
duality this dual program models because
二元性此双重程序模型是因为
there is no way to write messages to a
无法将消息写入
Kafka stream directly a Kafka stream
卡夫卡流直接卡夫卡流
Alton is just a topic and the way you
奥尔顿只是一个话题，你的方式
write messages to a Kafka stream or to a
将消息写入Kafka流或
topic in Kafka is just to write messages
Kafka中的主题只是写消息
to a topic right
正确的话题
Kafka streams is a API that you use when
Kafka流是您在以下情况下使用的API：
you're consuming data so we're gonna use
您正在使用数据，因此我们将使用
message channels and in traditional
消息渠道和传统
spring flood stream to write to Kafka
Spring 洪水要写给卡夫卡
but then on the on the other side we can
但另一方面，我们可以
use Kafka streams to process the data
使用Kafka流来处理数据
okay so let's see string want to call
好吧，让我们看一下字符串想要调用
this what I'm gonna call this this is
这就是我要称之为的
the this is going to be the page views
这将是页面浏览量
out channel so when a page views out
频道，因此当页面查看时
page views out alright so that's a
页面浏览量很好，所以这是一个
little long but it could just PV out
有点长，但它可能只是PV
let's do that okay so page views out
好吧，让页面浏览量变大
page views out and I'm going to tell the
页面浏览量，我将告诉
this class I'm gonna tell spring rather
这节课我要告诉 Spring
but I want to inject this type here in
但我想在这里注入这种类型
the constructor let's create a
构造函数让我们创建一个
constructor and we want to actually
构造函数，我们实际上想
inject the analytics binding binding so
注入分析绑定绑定，以便
binding dot pay trees out now in order
绑定点支付树现在按顺序
for spring cloud stream to know what to
让 Spring 的云流知道要做什么
do with this binding type we needs
使用我们需要的这种绑定类型
actually and analytics analytics binding
实际上和分析分析绑定
dot caffeine to enable the binding here
点咖啡因可在此处进行绑定
with that name of binding so what spring
那个绑定的名字，那么 Spring
constant we're gonna do is it's gonna
不变，我们要做的是
look at this interface it's gonna look
看看这个界面，它将
at the names of these channels and
这些频道的名称和
whatever the types or whatever bindings
任何类型或任何绑定
would put in this interface and it's
会放在这个界面中，
gonna look at the configuration you know
看一下你知道的配置
in the property file which we'll look at
在我们将要查看的属性文件中
in a second and it's gonna turn that
一秒钟，它会把那个
into a connection to our broker so let's
与我们的经纪人建立联系，让我们
do that let's go back to our brine upper
这样做，让我们回到盐水上层
our configuration file here we need to
我们的配置文件在这里，我们需要
configure a few things generically so
一般配置一些东西，这样
let's do some defaults first of all
首先让我们做一些默认设置
defaults
默认值
I want these to be things that apply to
我希望这些成为适用于
every message that sent into anywhere in
发送到任何地方的每条消息
our coffee between calcium Kafka code so
我们之间的咖啡钙卡夫卡代码如此
sprinkled stream Kafka streams dot
洒水卡夫卡流点
binary configuration commit off first
二进制配置先提交
all three commit that interval
所有三个提交该间隔
that ms equals a thousand so we'll have
毫秒等于一千，所以我们有
a committee interval of one second I
一秒钟的委员会间隔
want a default sterilization key so
需要一个默认的消毒钥匙，所以
default key sterilizer as a society in
作为一个社会的默认钥匙消毒器
Kafka pronounced so Saturday is a
卡夫卡（Kafka）宣布，所以星期六是一个
serializer and this year lesser so Cyr
序列化器，今年少了西尔
realizer
实现者
D sterilizer okay and you have to
D消毒器好了，你必须
specify that for keys and values now
现在为键和值指定
when we talk about keys and values in a
当我们谈论一个
Kafka context every message has a key
Kafka上下文中的每条消息都有一个密钥
that's associated with that message and
与该消息相关联的
it has a payment which is the value now
它有一个付款，现在的价值
Kafka doesn't care what those payloads
卡夫卡不在乎那些有效载荷
are or even what those keys are you have
是，甚至你有那些钥匙
to tell it that it's a it's an array of
告诉它这是一个数组
bytes or it's a string or you know you
个字节或一个字符串，或者您知道您
should use JSON or you should or you
应该使用JSON，或者您应该或者您
should use Avro which is actually a very
应该使用Avro这实际上是一个非常
common example a schema like a pro so
常见的例子是像pro这样的模式
that's something that you have to you
那是你必须拥有的
end up you're gonna find you have to
最后你会发现你必须
specify and worry about that a lot of
指定并担心很多
different places in you know when
你在不同的地方知道什么时候
working with Kafka so we're gonna
与Kafka合作，我们将
specify that up front because I don't
请事先指定，因为我没有
like to have to remember that only after
我想只记得
things are feeling okay so or look
事情看起来还不错，还是看
Apache Kafka common that's uh let it I
Apache Kafka的共同点，就是让我
don't remember sir days it's this class
先生，不记得是这节课
here we're gonna we're gonna reference a
在这里，我们要参考
we're gonna reference um it's just
我们将参考这个
Saturdays from this factory a class
这个工厂的星期六上课
called stare DES and we use there it is
叫做凝视DES，我们在那里使用它
for the key we're gonna use spring sorry
对于钥匙，我们将使用Spring 抱歉
string a real string Saturday and for
在周六为
the value we're going to use a default
我们将使用默认值的值
but value that's there there leave that
但那里的价值离开那
as well alright so there we go there's
好吧，所以我们去那里
our configuration default configuration
我们的配置默认配置
and now for this particular particular
现在针对这个特殊的
thing we're going to set up the binding
我们将要建立绑定的东西
for the the pageviews out okay so spring
网页浏览量还可以，所以 Spring
cloud stream bindings this is
云流绑定这是
traditional this is look this would look
传统，这是外观，这看起来
very familiar
非常熟悉
this is what you would have written even
这就是你甚至会写的
with with rabbitmq so sprinkled stream
与rabbitmq一起撒流
bindings dot what do we call this we
绑定点我们称之为什么
call this interface pv out
称此接口为PV
okay dot destination equals PV okay so I
好点的目的地等于PV好，所以我
want to say pageviews PV plural right
想说综合浏览量PV复数对
and we also want to specify that we
并且我们还想指定我们
should have well it configure some
应该配置好一些
things about the producer in particular
关于生产者的事情
we want to configure the header mode to
我们想要将标头模式配置为
be raw alright so there we go there's
好吧，所以我们去那里
our that's the the basis that we need
这就是我们需要的基础
for this let's see if that works so
为此，让我们看看是否可行
we're gonna now synthesize some data so
我们现在要合成一些数据，以便
let's think about how we do this can I
让我们考虑一下我们如何做到这一点
have some I'm gonna have some names here
有一些我要在这里有一些名字
names equals arrays dot as lists and
名称等于数组点作为列表，并且
it'll be um it'll be some names to be um
会是um会是一些名字
J long sure and a P web and so be
我很确定还有一个P网，因此
chuckles SCH AC kill Abel on o0tg
轻笑SCH AC在o0tg杀死Abel
Russell okay so we've got a few people
罗素好吧，我们有几个人
here sample names that's actually in
这里实际上是示例名称
Fisher there we are some of the folks
费舍尔，我们有些人
working on the messaging side of things
在消息传递方面工作
and so on I can we don't need to be
等等，我可以不必
there alright good so there's our names
那里很好，所以有我们的名字
and then there's some pages okay so some
然后有一些页面可以
pages on the website so let's say it's
网站上的页面，所以说
the blog you know sitemap English I sure
您知道的博客Sitemap英语我确定
hope because all the websites all good
希望因为所有网站都很好
web sites will have a spring initializer
网站将有一个Spring 初始化器
of course news khalaf on do people have
当然，人们有新闻快讯
website kala finds they should really
网站kala发现他们应该
and what else what else do we want about
还有什么我们想要的
sure okay so we have some names now now
好的，所以现在我们有了一些名字
what we're going to do is we're going to
我们要做的是
generate we're going to run a thread
生成我们要运行一个线程
that that um that will periodically
那个会定期
write some data to the message queue
将一些数据写入消息队列
right and so that thread is gonna be run
对，这样线程就可以运行
by a executor that will will send a rest
由遗嘱执行人送出休息
message using the front of all every one
使用所有人的正面的留言
second and there we go there's our
其次，我们去那里是我们的
runnable now we need to actually save
现在可以运行了，我们需要实际保存
some data so let's do that it's int
一些数据，所以我们做的是int
let's see we want to get the random name
让我们看看我们想获得随机名称
and a random page so our page equals new
和一个随机页面，因此我们的页面等于new
random dot next int and the number that
随机点next int和
when to spend other the pages size and
何时花费其他页面大小和
that's a number so let's turn that
那是一个数字，所以让我们开始
number in two pages dot gets and then
两页中的数字点获取，然后
our name names dot size alright so that
我们的名字叫点大小好，这样
looks like that'll be correct right so
看起来那将是正确的，所以
random page random name and we'll send
随机页面的随机名称，我们将发送
that data in a message which we'll build
这些数据将在我们将构建的消息中
here so a message builder dot with
这里是一个消息生成器点
payload and the payload of course is
有效载荷，有效载荷当然是
going to be an object of type page view
将成为页面视图类型的对象
event tonight so let's do that new page
今晚有活动，让我们做一个新页面
view event and we'll say that the name
查看事件，我们会说这个名字
is random name on the page is random
是页面上的随机名称是随机的
page and the duration in this case just
页面和持续时间在这种情况下
so we have something with which to work
所以我们有一些需要配合的东西
later it will be either ten or a
以后将是十个或一个
thousand why why not let's just we want
一千个为什么为什么不让我们就这样
to have something that we can bifurcate
有一些我们可以分叉的东西
the data with so as long as it's longer
只要更长的数据
than greater than ten we'll filter it
大于十的我们将对其进行过滤
out later okay so I'm gonna say page
以后出去好吧，我要说页面
view event I want to set a header and
查看事件我想设置标题和
that header is gonna be a key so I'm
该标题将是一个关键，所以我
gonna say Kafka headers dot message key
要说卡夫卡标题点消息密钥
and the key in this case will be the the
在这种情况下，关键是
view the name rather the page view event
查看名称而不是页面查看事件
don't get user ID Duncan bytes and then
没有获得用户ID Duncan字节，然后
we're gonna build the record okay so
我们会建立记录好吗
i'll give us an object that we can then
我会给我们一个对象，然后
send on that output channel so now we
发送该输出通道，所以现在我们
can do that so this the page views out
可以做到这一点，以便该页面可以查看
dot send message everyone out okay so
点向所有人发送消息，这样
there's our record there's our data
有我们的记录就有我们的数据
there's there's everything that we
有一切，我们
expect all right now let's go ahead and
期待现在一切，让我们继续前进，
see what that gives us now i'm gonna go
看看现在能给我们带来什么，我要去
ahead and wrap this in a try-catch
提前将其包装在try-catch中
because it's quiet if you don't catch
因为如果你不抓的话它很安静
any errors you won't know about it so
您不会知道的任何错误
let's just do that log dot error we need
让我们来做我们需要的那个日志点错误
a logger I guess we can use that log and
一个记录器，我想我们可以使用该记录了，
here log dot
这里的日志点
info was our error no they went to the
信息是我们的错误，不，他们去了
other one don't we
另一个不是吗
log4j love extern comments log Wow girl
log4j爱情extern评论日志哇女孩
is it yes that what is this one actually
是的，这实际上是什么？
give you whatever let's just do it the
给你任何让我们做的
manual a hair private final log log
手动发私人最终日志日志
equals factory don't get log good class
等于工厂没有获得良好的日志
voila so I'm now we have this log it
瞧，所以我现在有这个日志了
seems to be upset Oh wrong log bye to
似乎很沮丧哦错误的登录再见
you you goody all right so there's this
你，你好，好吧，这是
and now we say a log dot error you all
现在我们说一个对数点错误
right
对
so that'll be any if there's any
这样就可以了
encoding problems wouldn't send this
编码问题不会发送此
message out will find it very quickly
留言将很快找到它
all right so we're gonna schedule this
好吧，我们要安排这个
thread every one second we'll send out a
线程每隔一秒钟发送一次
new record with a random name and around
随机名称和周围的新记录
at random user and a random page see
在随机用户和随机页面上看到
what happens
怎么了
not seeing any errors I suppose I should
我没有看到任何错误，我应该
have had a confirmatory sort of message
收到确认消息
here so log that info sent message that
在这里记录信息发送的消息
to string okay
串好
all right so there's a message that's
好的，所以有一个消息是
sent it's got a page you event you can
发送有一个页面，你可以
see it's got random names and users
看到它有随机的名称和用户
random durations etc so now with that we
随机持续时间等，所以现在我们
have a feed of data that we can then
有一个数据源，我们可以
process we want to process this data
我们要处理这些数据的过程
using Kafka stream so again we're using
使用Kafka流，所以我们再次使用
Kafka streams Kafka streams is a
卡夫卡流卡夫卡流是
processing API it's a stream processing
处理API是流处理
API it can be used to do a lot of the
API，可以用来做很多
same things that you would otherwise
你本来会做的同样的事情
think about using things like a Apache
考虑使用类似Apache的东西
storm or or spark or or something like
暴风雨或火花或类似的东西
this these are stream processing engines
这些是流处理引擎
but there's a there's a big difference
但是有很大的不同
here in order to use Kafka streams all
这里为了使用卡夫卡流所有
you need is Kafka stream is a library it
您需要的是Kafka流是一个图书馆吗
is just a library it runs in the context
只是它在上下文中运行的库
of your application on your machine on
您的计算机上的应用程序
in the same note it doesn't need a
在同一笔记中，它不需要
separate cluster it doesn't need a
单独的集群，不需要
separate processing topology doesn't
单独的处理拓扑不会
need a custom serialization fabric for
需要一个自定义序列化结构
your your workloads or whatever it runs
您的工作量或运行量
in your code and so you can hang off
在您的代码中，因此您可以挂断电话
Kafka streams processing off the side of
Kafka将处理流从
your sort of spring boot app as we are
像我们这样的 spring boot 应用程序
here and take advantage of that with
在这里，并利用它
them with no extra of complications
他们没有额外的并发症
right it's just a library that's present
对，这只是一个存在的图书馆
on the fast path and it's a programming
在快速的道路上，这是一个编程
model so it integrates very nicely with
模型，因此可以很好地与
any other JVM code you've got and that
您拥有的任何其他JVM代码，以及
makes it invaluable that means you can
使其变得无价，这意味着您可以
deploy this application you know easily
轻松部署此应用程序
you can take this this is just a regular
你可以拿这个，这只是一个常规
spring with applications you can take
Spring ，您可以采取的应用程序
this and you know you connect this to
这，你知道你连接到
conflict cloud you know the hosted
您知道托管的冲突云
version of Apache Kafka from confluence
合流的Apache Kafka版本
the company behind Kafka you could
卡夫卡背后的公司，你可以
deploy this you could you could get an
部署这个，你可以得到一个
account on conflict cloud and then
在冲突云上帐户，然后
expose that to your application running
暴露给正在运行的应用程序
on cloud vendor and web services for
在云供应商和Web服务上
example right you can talk to that you
您可以与之交谈的示例权利
can deploy this easily to any public
可以轻松地将其部署到任何公众
infrastructure and it would be just fine
基础设施，那就很好了
you don't have to worry about 13 out how
您不必担心13
to deploy spark and all their networking
部署Spark及其所有网络
requirements and all that stuff this is
要求和所有这些东西是
just a regular Springwood application
只是常规的Springwood应用程序
there is state of course there's still
当然有状态
state but that state is kept in the
状态，但该状态保持在
broker all you ever need to be able to
经纪所有您需要的能力
run this code to go the process with
运行此代码以进行处理
Kafka streams is Kafka that's it once
卡夫卡流是卡夫卡就这样
you figure out how to get that installed
你弄清楚如何安装
which in the case of confluent cloud is
在融合云的情况下是
super you know super simple once you
超级，一旦你知道超级简单
have that figured out you're done Europe
知道你完成了欧洲
you're off to the races the state is
你去参加比赛了
kept in-between processing it's kept in
保持在处理之间
state stores inside of Kafka itself or
卡夫卡本身内部的国家商店或
it's kept in topics or it's kept in you
它被保存在主题中，或者被保存在您体内
know various various nooks and crannies
知道各种各样的角落和缝隙
in side of your Kafka broker itself and
在您的Kafka经纪人本身和
the replication of that state is done
该状态的复制已完成
for you guys it by guess what Kafka so
对你们来说，猜猜卡夫卡是什么
again if you have Kafka if you of all if
如果您拥有卡夫卡，那么再次
you figured out the recipe for scaling
你想出了扩大规模的秘诀
out or prioritizing and working with
或优先处理
Kafka then you are done right I don't
卡夫卡，那么你做对了，我不
need for anything extra and that state
需要任何额外的东西和那个状态
is useful as well see here so let's
也很有用，请看这里，让我们
create a um a spring cuts combining for
创建一个umSpring 切割组合
the incoming messages so the messages
传入的消息，所以消息
are going to be of type string that's
将是字符串类型的
the the user ID here and the payload
这里的用户ID和有效负载
will be page view event okay so I'm
可以进行网页浏览活动，所以我
gonna create a Kafka stream binder or
将创建Kafka流活页夹或
binding for that so it's at input and
为此绑定，因此在输入和
I'm gonna create a new variable here
我要在这里创建一个新变量
page views in TV in page views in and
和中的电视浏览量中的电视浏览量
it'll be K stream and stream page view
这将是K流和流页面视图
event page views in alright so there's
活动页面浏览量还可以，因此
your incoming message your incoming
您的传入消息您的传入消息
Kafka stream and this Kafka stream
卡夫卡流和此卡夫卡流
obviously is you know this is the API
显然您知道这是API
you can create this yourself alright
你可以自己创建这个
there's a that that that come that
有一个那个来
tedious configuration is being done
繁琐的配置正在完成
filled by spring class stream in this
在这个 Spring 的课堂流中充满
case and the wiring I will see it for
案例和布线，我会看到它
this is done external to so there's no
这是在外部完成的，因此没有
mention of topics in this code we just
在此代码中提及主题
and we have a typed object that we can
我们有一个类型化的对象，我们可以
work with let's do page views in alright
让我们一起进行页面浏览
so here we are and in the on the
所以我们在这里，在
incoming side we're going to have the
传入端，我们将拥有
basically the same thing is this same
基本上是一样的东西
same thing on this but in Reverse so P V
同样的事情，但在反向所以PV
in be V in and it's a consumer not a
成为消费者，而不是消费者
producer whose headers shall be wrong
标头错误的生产者
right so that's that's I think all we
对，那就是我想我们
need for that let's go ahead and see
为此，让我们继续看看
what happens
怎么了
we need to actually process this data
我们需要实际处理这些数据
now so we defined the binding but the
现在，我们定义了绑定，但是
best part about this is that we can now
最好的部分是我们现在可以
use this binding to process the data so
使用此绑定来处理数据，以便
let's create a a spring crud stream
让我们创建一个Spring Crud Stream
processing sink so our page views
处理接收器，因此我们的页面浏览量
event sync okay and this is going to be
事件同步好，这将是
a stream listener public void process
流侦听器公共无效过程
that input analytics binding class
输入分析绑定类
that's alright that page views in and
没关系，而且
we'll have K stream stream page view
我们将有K个流流页面视图
event events okay let's do that
事件事件好吧，让我们这样做
so now private final log log factory get
所以现在私人最终日志工厂日志
logged already so there's our incoming
已经登录了，所以我们的传入
messages events and what we want to do
消息事件以及我们想要做什么
is want to take that data and work with
想获取这些数据并与之合作
it so let's see events dot and we know
因此，让我们看点事件，我们知道
that we're gonna have data that's going
我们将要获得的数据
to come in and we want to filter it
进来，我们想过滤它
first of all I want to say filter a new
首先，我想说过滤一个新的
predicate or provide a predicate object
谓词或提供谓词对象
there of type string and page view and
有类型的字符串和页面视图和
event by the way these are the Kafka
这些都是卡夫卡事件
streams types these are not from Java 8
这些不是来自Java 8的流类型
so this works in in theoretically this
所以这在理论上是有效的
works in older API is older JVMs
在较旧的API中工作的是较旧的JVM
although realistically freezing spring
虽然实际上冻结了 Spring
butyou're in a java 8 world
但是你在Java 8世界中
if using pre Muto which you all should
如果使用前Muto，你们都应该
be by the way now that it's out of GA
顺便说一句，因为它不在通用航空中
you're in the Java 8 plus world anyway
无论如何，您在Java 8 plus世界中
so we're gonna say value dot get
所以我们要说价值点得到
duration get duration is greater than
持续时间获取持续时间大于
where do we say ten seconds so there's
我们在哪里说十秒钟，所以
our first bit the lambda there and if
我们的第一位lambda在那里，如果
and if we've done that then we want to
如果我们做到了，那么我们想
map I want to say I want a map the I'm
我想说我想要一张地图
gonna repartition the data so I'm gonna
要重新分配数据，所以我要
I have a stream of records so the each
我有记录流，所以每个
record will pass through this filter
记录将通过此过滤器
method then it'll be passed to this one
方法，然后将其传递给此方法
and here I'm gonna repartition the
在这里我要分区
stream I'm gonna say ok the new key and
流，我要说确定新密钥，
value that you should manage is going to
您应该管理的价值
be oriented around the page and the
围绕页面和
count so I'm gonna say the value dot get
计数，所以我要说值点得到
page and this I could just do 0 who
页，这我可以做0谁
cares well well we don't actually even
很好，我们实际上甚至都没有
want the the number we don't even want
想要我们甚至不想要的号码
the value anymore what we care about is
我们关心的是价值
the count so now we're going to create a
计数，所以现在我们要创建一个
count
计数
okay so let's actually just
好吧，让我们实际上只是
clean this coat up a bit here we're
在这里把这件外套打扫干净
playing with replace with lambda don't
玩用lambda代替不要
even need that good and now we're going
甚至需要那种好东西，现在我们要去
to store some data here so we're going
在这里存储一些数据，所以我们要
to say they want to create a count of
说他们想创造一个
all the records in the in the stream
流中的所有记录
okay in order to create that count I
好，以便创建该计数
need to group by I want to group by like
需要分组我想分组
yeah the key in this case I can go by
是的，在这种情况下，关键是我可以通过
using custom key value mapper if I like
如果我喜欢使用自定义键值映射器
where the output type is the string or
输出类型是字符串或
the Panther that I want use as a key so
我想用作按键的豹
here it would be string string you know
这是你知道的字符串
etc so the key the value and all I want
等，所以关键的价值和我想要的
to do is just partition by the key well
要做的只是按好键分区
that's a there's a shortcut syntax for
这是一个快捷语法
then of course I could do a lambda but
那我当然可以做一个lambda但是
there's even one that's even better just
甚至有一个甚至更好
goodbye key and now I want to store that
再见密钥，现在我要存储
count and that count is stateful
计数，并且该计数是有状态的
remember what we're gonna do is where
记住我们要做的是在哪里
every time a message comes by every
每当每一个消息传来
every time a message comes through this
每次有消息通过
processing flow that has this key
具有此密钥的处理流程
whatever key is in this case it's the
在这种情况下，关键是
page so let's say that a message comes
页面，所以假设有一条消息
in and the page is initializer well I
在和页面初始化好我
want to keep a count of that what do I
想要保持计数，我该怎么办
keep that I don't want to keep it in the
保持，我不想保留在
same note on the JVM post this here
JVM上的相同注释在此发布
itself I'm going to keep that in the
本身，我将其保留在
broker
经纪人
so that'll there's actually a whole
所以实际上有一个整体
persistent subsystem that is you know
你知道的持久子系统
it's it's exposed to you not just to
这是暴露给你的，而不仅仅是
this idea of a topic but also through
这个话题的想法还可以通过
this idea of a materialized view so I
这个物化视图的想法，所以我
want to keep that count and then
想要保持该数量，然后
increment the number so I'm going to say
增加数字，所以我要说
materialized as and I'll give it a name
体现为，我给它起一个名字
I'll give it a string page views sorry
我给它一个字符串页面浏览量
page count materialized view all right
页数实例化视图可以
so I'm going to use analytics binding
所以我将使用分析绑定
there okay that constant page count
那里的页面数不变
materialized views all right
物化视图可以
MD whatever so we we don't need to do
MD等等，所以我们不需要做
anything to configure the materialized
可以配置的任何东西
view but that's nice because we'll find
视图，但这很好，因为我们会发现
out later that we can actually
后来我们可以
interrogate this matthias view would
审讯这种matthias的观点
actually query it as an independent of
实际上以独立于
this messaging abstraction that that
这个消息传递的抽象
just Kafka gives you so that count is
只是卡夫卡给你，所以计数是
now if you look at if you look at the
现在，如果你看，如果你看
return the return value that comes from
返回来自的返回值
that count call you get something called
算数电话，你得到的东西叫做
a K table and a k table is a different
K表和ak表是不同的
thing than a case stream a case stream
事例比事例流
is a continuous sequence of messages
是连续的消息序列
and some may be the same exact you know
有些可能与您所知道的完全相同
they may have the same data and key as
它们可能具有与以下相同的数据和密钥
previous messages but it doesn't matter
以前的消息，但这没关系
it's a continuous ongoing sort of
这是持续不断的
unbounded stream where as a cake table
无界的流作为蛋糕桌
is and it's always gonna be the latest
是，而且永远都是最新的
value of a given key all right so a case
给定键的值可以，在这种情况下
stream will have maybe five or ten
流可能有五个或十个
messages for the same key maybe they all
相同键的消息可能全部
maybe they have different values maybe
也许他们有不同的价值观，也许
they don't but you'll have you'll be
他们没有，但你会拥有你
able to if you lose the case string
如果您丢失大小写字符串，则能够
you'll be able to get access to all ten
您将可以访问全部十个
of those messages with the same key with
那些具有相同密钥的消息
the K table you'd have one entry for the
K表中您将有一个条目
key and then the latest observe value
键，然后是最新的观察值
for that key right so this is like at a
对于那个关键的权利，所以这就像在
time like a database table it's a change
时间像数据库表一样
log versus the the sequence of events
日志与事件顺序
that led to that change and so we can
导致了变化，所以我们可以
actually process things with this K
用这个K实际处理事物
table and that's interesting in of
表，这很有趣
itself but what I actually want to do is
本身，但我真正想做的是
I'm gonna take this data which is coming
我要获取即将到来的数据
from a K table and turn it into a stream
从K表转为流
and then send those results to another
然后将这些结果发送给另一个
topic so that we can then on the other
主题，以便我们可以在另一方面
side process them as it came k table in
一边处理它们，一边进入k表
another piece of code now there's a lot
另一段代码现在有很多
of you know there's a the distinction
你们当中有一个区别
here is very interesting the distinction
这是非常有趣的区别
between a case stream and a K table is a
案例流和K表之间是
one of the reasons that Kafka streams is
卡夫卡流的原因之一是
so so powerful that duality leads to a
如此强大以至于二元性导致
lot of really really powerful
很多真的很强大
opportunities the the the in Kafka
卡夫卡的机会
streams things can go from one to the
流事物可以从一个流到另一个
other very fluidly so I can have a Kafka
其他非常流畅，所以我可以有一个卡夫卡
stream that uh that shows me all the
流向我展示所有
events that led to something and I can
导致某事的事件，我可以
have a table that shows me the the
有一张桌子给我看
change you know the final values for
更改您知道的最终值
those things as recorded well I can also
那些东西记录得很好，我也可以
then turn that that list of final values
然后把那个最终值列表
into events right so I can actually I
进入事件，所以我实际上可以
can do things like you know events
可以做你知道的事情
sourcing very very naturally in this way
以这种方式非常自然地采购
you might have for example a Kafka
你可能有一个卡夫卡
stream that has all of the all of the
具有所有
people that have ever flown a flight
曾经飞行的人
right whereas the Kafka table could show
正确，而卡夫卡表可以显示
you how many people
你多少人
have flown over a year for example or
例如，飞行了一年或
over a month to different countries same
一个多月到不同国家
thing so you could you could say given a
东西，所以你可以说给定一个
country show me the count of people that
国家让我知道人数
have gone to that country and and this
已经去那个国家了，这个
brings us to another point here I have
带我们到另一个地方
shown you a count here and that count is
向您显示了一个计数，这个计数是
an absolute number in this case this K
在这种情况下，绝对数为K
table is an absolute number it's just
表是一个绝对数字
gonna be you know for every every
你会知道每一个
message ever seen
见过的消息
show me the count but maybe I don't want
给我看看计数，但也许我不想
that maybe I want to actually get a
也许我想真正得到一个
count for everything in the last hour
算上最后一个小时的一切
right and I can actually do that I can
对，我实际上可以做到
say windowed by time windows dot of
说由时间窗点
let's say a thousand milliseconds right
比方说一千毫秒吧
I'm a second or sixty seconds a minute
我一分钟一秒钟或六十秒
so now I've got a windowed table right
所以现在我有一个开窗的桌子
that's actually a slightly different
这实际上有点不同
Friday you can see it's a key table of
星期五，您可以看到它是
windowed long so it'll show me if I
窗口很长，所以会告诉我是否
query this if I pull the state out the
如果我将状态拉出
other side it'll actually show me time
另一面实际上会告诉我时间
gaps it'll show me you know from from
差距会告诉我你从中知道
this hour to this hour and then from
这个小时到这个小时，然后从
this era like this hour and then this
像这个小时然后这个时代
hour this hour that's the number you'll
这个小时就是你将要拨打的号码
get you'll get a seek an array of
得到你会寻求一个数组
windows of windowed with keys and then
带有键的窗口，然后
you'll be able to pull out the value for
您将能够提取出
that window for the particular time
在特定时间的那个窗口
group and this is very convenient
团体，这很方便
because you can do things like um I can
因为你可以做像我一样的事情
bucket data you can say okay this is the
桶数据，你可以说好吧，这是
processing time right this is the time
现在是处理时间了
that or rather this is the event time
那就是事件的时间
this is the event time that this thing
这是这个东西的活动时间
happened you know in the real world and
发生在现实世界中，
I want to be able to figure out what
我想弄清楚什么
that looks like
看起来像
later on retro actively in terms of you
后来对你积极地回溯
know I can run justice statistics over I
知道我可以对我进行司法统计
can process that data I can use that
可以处理我可以使用的数据
data to figure out how often things are
数据以找出事物发生的频率
happening and that state is also
发生，那个状态也是
something you have to keep somewhere and
有些东西你必须留在某个地方
this is where it's nice to have this
这是有这个的好地方
sort of unified persistence approach
一种统一的持久性方法
right so you could even you know these
对，所以你甚至可以知道这些
TK tables you could originate K tables
您可以起源K表的TK表
by you could actually create a K table
您实际上可以创建一个K表
by reading the data records from a
通过从
database it might be even a fixed
数据库甚至可能是固定的
database but you can put it into a K
数据库，但您可以将其放入K
table and then the best part is once you
桌子，然后最好的部分是一旦你
have these K tables and they're you know
有这些K表，他们是你知道的
they're they're established you can join
他们是他们建立的，你可以加入
K tables so I can have a K table that
K表，所以我可以有一个K表
join on another K table left a left join
在另一个K表上联接，左联接
you know outer join the Tetra
你知道外加入利乐
and same thing for a case stream so it's
对于案件流也是如此，
I don't have a case stream here oh I do
我这里没有案子哦，我知道
much I can say events dot join K table
我可以说很多事件点连接K表
and that would join the events on the
那将加入事件
left with the the the records in the K
留下了K中的记录
table on the right by their T so as long
在他们的T右边的桌子上，只要
as the K table has the same key as the
因为K表的键与
one on the events then they will be
一个事件，那么他们将
matched up and I'll get the result this
匹配，我将得到结果
is let's see ok table this is a silly
是让我们看看确定表，这是一个愚蠢的
example but if I did that what do I have
例子，但是如果我做到了，我有什么
here K table etc and then you can
在这里K表等，然后你可以
provide a new value jointer so new value
提供新的价值竞合者，使新的价值
jointer or even better yet just to left
联合甚至更好，但只剩下
join K table and new value jointer
加入K表和新价值联合
and so on so the the result is you get a
依此类推，结果是您得到了
stream or whatever you whatever the
流或随便你
result is and this is the you know the
结果是，这是你知道的
value on the left and the value on the
左边的值和
right and I'm supposed to aggregate them
对，我应该将它们汇总
in some way and of course I might have
以某种方式，当然我可能有
no left join you know it means I have
没有左加入，你知道这意味着我有
one of everything on the left but I
左边的一切之一，但我
might have some missing matches on the
可能会缺少一些匹配项
right for example so you know just like
例如，所以你知道就像
a sequel database just like a relational
像关系数据库一样的续集数据库
database if you've worked at these kinds
数据库（如果您曾经从事过此类工作）
of idioms before and now you have full
以前的成语现在你已经吃饱了
control on the resulting stream let's
控制结果流让我们
say this is a string okay let's say
说这是一个字符串好吧，让我们说
somehow I got a string under that I can
不知何故我得到了一个字符串，我可以
say
说
is a steam a resulting stream of string
是蒸汽，产生的串流
of string or it may be a better example
或可能是一个更好的例子
is a date or something I mean so you can
是约会或其他意思，所以您可以
understand what's happening here
了解这里发生了什么
date date right so now this becomes a
日期日期对，所以现在这变成了
string to date match which is really
迄今为止的字符串匹配
powerful right now you can do some on
强大的功能，您现在可以在
you know these are both moving targets
你知道这两个都是移动目标
right there both continually updating
那里都在不断更新
but now you have the ability to in
但是现在你有能力
memory or in in in flight
记忆中或飞行中
do these joins between two different
在两个不同的地方做这些连接
disparate data sets you can do
您可以做的不同的数据集
correlation you can say okay well you
相关性你可以说很好
know first of all here's all the the
首先知道这里的所有
people that have clicked on a particular
点击了特定内容的人
page and then over here here's a K table
页面，然后在这里是K表
that shows you the the you know the
告诉你你知道的
related information about that page for
有关该页面的相关信息
example you know or people you can break
你认识的人或可以打破的人
down the user information maybe I've got
记录下用户信息，也许我已经
user information here I can say okay
这里的用户信息我可以说还可以
here's the they page view impressions
这是他们的网页浏览量
and then I can join that to a list of
然后我可以将其加入到
all the geography distributions for
的所有地理分布
different people different users I can
不同的人，不同的用户，我可以
say San Francisco and the person to that
说旧金山和那个人
city and I can o arrange so that both am
城市，我可以安排，以便双方
joined on the user ID and I can find out
加入了用户ID，我可以找到
how many people visit a particular page
有多少人访问特定页面
from given regions for example right you
例如，来自给定的区域
can do some very very sophisticated
可以做一些非常非常复杂的事情
things by by taking advantage of that
通过利用这一点
joining capability and the fact that
连接能力和事实
you've got these key tables versus
你有这些关键表与
streams but they are they are ultimately
流，但他们是他们最终
both backed by topics okay so that's
两者都有主题支持，所以
what we want to do is want to take this
我们想要做的就是要接受这个
data and turn it into a stream and send
数据并将其转换为流并发送
that stream back to send the results of
流返回以发送结果
that stream to another topic so I'm
流到另一个主题，所以我
going to say a case stream of string
要说一串字符串
long and we're gonna say at send to and
很久，我们要说的发送到和
it's going to be page counts out all
这将是全部页面数
right so analytics binding that page
正确，因此分析功能可以绑定该页面
count out page count out okay that
数出页面数出来好吗
constant PC out and we'll to in because
不断的PC退出，我们将进入
we know that's coming all right
我们知道一切都会好起来的
so going back to the code here we need
所以回到这里的代码
to change our our processor so there's
改变我们的处理器，所以
this case stream and we need to return
这种情况下，我们需要返回
the data so return
数据如此返回
like that all right yeah that's a little
像那样，是的，有点
easier to read there you go that's a
更容易阅读到那里，这是一个
little bit better so we're saying
好一点，所以我们说
process the data coming in for the
处理输入的数据
pageviews that's gonna give us one kind
网页浏览量会给我们一种
of stream we're gonna turn that into
流，我们要把它变成
another kind of stream in this in this
在这另一种流
case it's a stream of pages two counts
情况下这是两个计数的页面流
right and it's the total count and then
对，这是总数，然后
I'm turning that list of that I'm
我要列出的是
turning that table into a stream so now
把那张桌子变成溪流，所以现在
I'm gonna get a there's a new topic this
我会得到一个新的话题
new topic will have all the keys and
新主题将包含所有键和
anytime the key changes I'll get a new
任何时候只要有关键变化我都会得到一个新的
record
记录
all right so if the key is you know the
好吧，所以如果关键是你知道
initializer and the first value is one
初始值设定项，第一个值是一个
I'll get it I'll get a new record for
我会得到一个新记录的
one and then if somebody sets that
一个然后如果有人设置
record to be you know if they're if the
记录下来，以了解他们是否
count increases - what - then I'll get a
计数增加-什么-然后我会得到
new record for that etc but I won't get
该等的新记录，但我不会
the you know I think I want to get to
你知道我想我要去
every single event I'll just get the
每个事件我都会得到
changes right four counts alright so
更改正确的四个计数，所以
there's that now we need to actually
现在我们需要
configure this this output channel this
配置这个输出通道这个
output binding here so I'm just I'm
输出绑定在这里，所以我就是
forwarding the message here this is a
在这里转发消息，这是一个
processor then he actually should call
处理器，那么他实际上应该调用
this a processor in messaging puddles
这是消息传递池中的处理器
page.you event processor and I'm going
page.you事件处理器，我要去
to send this the page count out and the
发送此页面计数和
page count out binding is going to be
页面计数绑定将是
just that it's going to be a a a case
只是这将是aaa案例
dream but we're treating it like a yeah
梦想，但我们把它当作是
it's a key stream that we're gonna send
这是我们要发送的密钥流
out so output and page count out K
出，因此输出和页数出K
stream string long page count out all
流字符串长页全部计数
right so there's that there's a page
对，所以有一个页面
count out and now we are going to
算出来，现在我们要
process that data so we want to process
处理这些数据，所以我们要处理
that data coming in so we now also have
数据输入，所以我们现在也有了
a input K table so input page count in
输入K表，因此输入页数
and here we're going to define a K table
这里我们要定义一个K表
of type string too long so page count in
类型的字符串太长，因此页数在
all right
好吧
so now we do we need to configure the
所以现在我们需要配置
page counts for out and in so let's do
页数进出，让我们开始吧
that in a config file so page counts out
在配置文件中，以便页面计数
and let's see page counts in and for the
让我们来看看
for the config this gets a little bit
对于配置，这会有点
more tedious we have to actually specify
更麻烦的是我们必须实际指定
a fair amount of configuration here but
这里有很多配置，但是
we do get a lot of benefits for that so
为此我们确实获得了很多好处
at least it at least we know it's a you
至少它至少我们知道它是你
know there's a gain to that it's not
知道这样做是有好处的
something that we want miring our code
我们想要镜像我们的代码的东西
with complexity so much better to have
非常复杂
it as a configuration parameter so here
它作为配置参数，所以这里
we're gonna say spring cloud stream
我们要说 Spring 的云流
bindings dot what do we say we called it
绑定点我们怎么说我们称之为
um PC out PC out dot destination equals
um PC out PC out点目标等于
pcs let's just call that going with a
个，让我们称之为
theme here and the PC out dot producer
主题和PC输出点生产者
dot use native encoding equals true and
点使用本机编码等于true和
then we need to specify the
那么我们需要指定
serialization for the key in the value
值中的键的序列化
for this particular channel so spring we
对于这个特定的频道，如此 Spring ，我们
can just copy this basic idea up here
可以在这里复制这个基本想法
its prefix all right so spring cloud
它的前缀好吧，所以 Spring 的云
stream binder a sprinkle stream cough
溪流粘合剂，洒水咳嗽
guy that streams the binder that
束缚者的家伙
bindings dot PC out dot producer dot
绑定点PC输出点生产者点
values are they in key third a so the
值是关键三分之一，所以
key so de is gonna be very similar to
关键，所以德将非常类似于
this it's gonna be a string third a but
这将是三分之一弦，但是
here we're gonna use a long sir de cera
在这里，我们要用一个很长的塞拉先生
day all right so there's the key in the
一天没事，所以钥匙里有钥匙
value sir there and when you do the same
价值先生在那里，当你做同样的
thing on the other side as well it'll
另一面的东西也会
probably still work even if I don't
即使我不这样做也可能仍然可以工作
bother but we do need to get this done
麻烦，但我们确实需要完成这项工作
so might as well do it now
所以现在就做吧
the main bits the main different here of
主要位在这里主要不同
course it's the same same destination
当然是同一目的地
right so we knew that's fine PC out PC
对，所以我们知道那是很好的PC
in and PC in again and here we also need
并再次插入PC，在这里我们还需要
a group an exclusive consumer group so
一群专属的消费群体
I'm going to say that the group is going
我要说的是该小组正在
to be called just peace yes that's a
被称为和平，是的
problem
问题
and here I'm gonna specify PC end PC end
这里我要指定PC端PC端
consumer consumer key sir that's a
消费者消费者关键先生
jumped all right so that gives us a
跳得很好，所以给了我们一个
destination we're using native encoding
我们使用本地编码的目的地
we want to specify the header mode of
我们要指定的标头模式
course so the header mode whoops wrong
当然，标题模式会出错
one I want to specify this one is that
我要指定的一个是
right let's bring close dreams right no
对吧，让我们带来梦想吧
I want to specify this one so consumer
我想指定一个这样的消费者
dots header mode equals raw and here
点头模式等于原始模式
this is a consumer as well because it's
这也是一个消费者，因为
the incoming data so we've got consumers
传入的数据，所以我们有消费者
everywhere equals true right let's see
到处都是正确的权利，让我们看看
is that all that's us one two three four
就是我们一二三四
five six so that looks about right I
五六，所以看起来不错我
think that's about right that's all we
认为那是对的，仅此而已
need to make this work
需要做这项工作
content type movie suppose for the
影片内容类型假定为
content type I'm I'm never really sure
内容类型我不确定
content type is equal to application
内容类型等于应用程序
JSON sure okay now there we go we have
JSON可以，现在可以了
our we have the updated configuration we
我们有更新的配置
now have a page count in and out we have
现在有一个页面进出我们
a page views in and out let's move that
进出页面的页面让我们移动
up here to be with its related thing
在这里与其相关的东西
page views page counts output page count
页面浏览量页面计数输出页面计数
out input page count in and that's it
输入页面数出来，仅此而已
that's the configuration for now if this
这是现在的配置，如果这
goes correctly we should now be able to
正确进行，我们现在应该能够
write a bit of code that processes the
编写一些代码来处理
data coming from the K table right so
数据来自K表，所以
add component public static class page
添加组件公共静态类页面
count sync alright and here we're going
计数同步好了，我们要开始了
to have a stream listener and we'll say
有一个流监听器，我们会说
analytics binding dot page count in
分析绑定点页数
we went to public void process at input
我们在输入时进入了公共无效流程
and it'll be a key table string to long
这将是一个很长的关键表字符串
counts ready so there's this now we've
做好准备，所以现在我们有了
got counts and here in the counts
有计数，在计数中
section we're going to just visit the
部分，我们将只访问
data so we can say to stream I'm going
数据，所以我们可以说流我要去
to turn from a table to a stream and
从桌子变成小溪，
then we're gonna visit each one using
然后我们将使用
the new for each action I'm gonna log it
每个动作的新动作，我都会记录下来
out okay so we're just log out the data
退出，所以我们只是注销数据
just to confirm what we think is
只是为了确认我们的想法
happening so final log log equals log
发生，因此最终日志日志等于日志
factory don't get log already and that's
工厂尚未获取日志，那就是
just log everything out key a plus value
只需注销所有内容，再加上一个加值
so there's this let's see what we get is
所以有一个让我们看看我们得到的是
that gonna work that should that should
那应该工作，应该应该
work that seems simple enough we have
看起来很简单的工作
now page count sink that's processing
现在正在处理的页面计数接收器
the data that's gonna be sent from this
将要从中发送的数据
processing thing so the data is gonna
处理的东西，以便数据将
come in it's gonna be sent out from this
进来它会被发送出去
processor it'll be sent to the page
处理器，它将被发送到页面
count out topic and we can see that the
算出主题，我们可以看到
page count out topic is pointing to pcs
页面计数出主题指向个人电脑
that input then on the other side we're
然后在另一边输入
gonna have an input that process the
将有一个输入来处理
data from PC as now I'm doing this all
来自PC的数据，因为我现在正在做这一切
in the same application but as you can
在相同的应用程序中，但可以
imagine there is no reason that this
想象没有理由
could not be different sinks and sources
不能是不同的接收者和来源
in different micro services different
在不同的微服务中不同
applications each focused on one
每个应用程序专注于一个
particular aspect of the of the
的特定方面
application alright so that should be it
应用程序就可以了
let's see if that works we'll go ahead
让我们看看是否行得通
and just get that running
并开始运行
sending a message good hopefully it's
寄出一个好消息，希望是
going to work here
去这里工作
they're an errand here somewhere
他们在某处是差事
there we go look at that page counts
我们去看看那页数
Incas now getting data so you can see
印加人现在正在获取数据，因此您可以看到
it's it's these are the number of
这是这些的数量
messages that have been seen for a
曾经看到过的消息
particular page being reflected here in
特定页面反映在这里
the console okay so that's working and
控制台好，所以可以正常工作了
we're getting it we're periodically
我们得到它，我们定期
getting data from the table and it's
从表中获取数据，
showing us the aggregates now I want to
现在向我们展示聚合
I want to be able to inspect this data
我希望能够检查此数据
right this is it's nice that I have this
对，这很好，我有这个
ability to then corral the state of it I
然后能够掌握其状态的能力
actually remember what we said that data
真正记得我们所说的数据
is also being written to a state store
也被写到州立商店
right that's this thing right here that
对的就是这个东西
state store is queryable so that's quite
状态存储是可查询的，因此相当
a rest in point that that surfaces that
在表面上休息一下
information so at risk controller public
风险控制者要公开的信息
static class count rest controller all
静态类计数其余控制器全部
right and I'm going to inject the
对，我要注入
queryable store registry and creating a
可查询的商店注册表并创建一个
constructor argument here couldn't
构造函数参数不能在这里
endpoint get mapping I'm gonna call this
端点获取映射，我将其称为
the counts endpoint for lack of a better
缺乏更好的计数终点
name and it'll just be just that it'll
名称，只是它会
be counts and we'll call them back to
算数，我们会把它们叫回
that in a second map of string long
在第二个字符串long中
count equals new hash map all right
计数等于新的哈希图
reformat okay so we've got another
重新格式化好吧，我们还有另一个
counts and what I'm gonna do is I'm
计数，而我要做的就是
going to use that register I'm gonna say
要使用那个寄存器，我要说
this don't register dot get credible
这不注册点变得可信
store and I'm going to use the name that
商店，我将使用该名称
we created in the binding so page yeah
我们在绑定中创建了页面
sorry page count analytics bindings dot
抱歉，页面计数分析绑定点
page count MV and the kind of data I
页数MV和数据类型I
went back I have to specify a credible
回去，我必须指定一个可信的
store type the kind of data I want back
存储类型我想要返回的数据类型
is a key value store though that said
虽然是一个关键值存储
there are windows stores for example
有窗户商店例如
that we could you know that corresponds
我们可以知道对应
to the data that you would get if we had
如果我们拥有的话，您将获得的数据
used the window operator before in this
在此之前使用过窗口运算符
case we just have simple keys values so
情况下，我们只有简单的键值，所以
we'll pull that back out all right so um
我们会把它拉回来好吧
craveable store all right and the data
渴望存储所有数据
that it's coming back is a it's a key
它回来是一个关键
value like Redis of string too long
字符串的Redis等值太长
right so there's this and now I'm gonna
对，所以有这个，现在我要
visit that date I'm gonna say queryable
拜访那个日期我要说可查询的
store thoughts all that'll give me an
储存所有想法，这将使我
iterator
迭代器
and I'm gonna visit all the data while
我将在访问所有数据的同时
all that has next all dot next and we'll
所有下一个都有所有下一个点，我们将
store that okay so we're going to add
可以存储，所以我们要添加
this to a counts dot directory value dot
这到一个计数点目录值点
key value dot value and will return
键值点值，将返回
counts goody so there's our simple map
很重要，所以这里有我们的简单地图
we're just eating all the over the data
我们只是吃完所有数据
I'm going to surface that as a rest
我要休息一下
endpoint that somebody can then hit
然后有人可以击中的端点
while processing is happening to see
在处理过程中看到
where things stand so let's see what
情况如何，让我们看看
that looks like
看起来像
all right we got some data being
好吧，我们得到了一些数据
processed things are moving along it's
处理过的东西正在前进
being moved across the wire from one
从一根电线穿过
node to another and every now and then
到另一个节点，时不时地
we get some data there and now we go to
我们在那里得到一些数据，现在我们去
local host 8080 forward slash counts and
本地主机8080正斜杠计数和
we get this JSON that shows us the
我们得到此JSON，向我们显示
updating counts right the the data here
更新计数正确的数据在这里
is slowly but steadily updating to
正在缓慢但稳定地更新为
reflect what we're seeing in that in the
反映出我们在
table all right so we've looked at just
桌子好吧，所以我们只看了
a few things here we've looked at them
这里有几件事我们已经看过了
we've looked at a sprint countryman
我们看过一个冲刺的乡下人
Kafka although that was just a quick
卡夫卡，虽然那只是一个快速
revisitation of a review of what we
回顾对我们的回顾
looked at before when we talked about
在我们谈论之前看过
spring cloud stream and RabbitMQ and we
Spring Cloud Stream 和RabbitMQ，我们
looked at you know basic production of
看着你知道的基本生产
data into Kafka we talk about what Kafka
数据输入卡夫卡，我们谈论一下卡夫卡
itself is it's a very interesting
本身是非常有趣的
technology and um we're seeing it being
技术，嗯，我们看到了
used more and more increasingly it's
用的越来越多了
already powering thousands of different
已经为数以千计的不同提供动力
websites I remember this is now it's got
我记得这是现在的网站
to be a couple years now at least couple
至少要几年
years there was a big big story where
几年来有个大故事
Netflix was using Kafka and they were
Netflix正在使用Kafka，
doing something like a billion you know
做十亿左右的事
events a day or something like that
一天或类似的事件
something crazy right some crazy amount
疯狂的事，一些疯狂的事
of data passing through there Kafka
那里通过的数据集卡夫卡
systems no problem and that was years
系统没问题，那是几年
ago that was at least two years ago
至少在两年前
maybe more so now that's one thing that
也许更多，所以这是一回事
we looked at we looked at them spring
我们看着我们看着他们 Spring
cloud streaming Kafka then we looked at
云流卡夫卡，然后我们看了看
the
的
Kafka stream support right so we the
Kafka流支持正确，所以我们
Kafka stream support is is the key of
Kafka流支持是关键
what we're talking about here it's the
我们在这里谈论的是
essence of what we wanted to focus on
我们想要关注的重点
today it's the thing that allows us to
今天，让我们能够
write data and then process it to stream
写入数据，然后对其进行处理以流式传输
over it and that stream processing as we
在它上面，然后我们进行流处理
say is we know it's just embedded in our
说我们知道它只是嵌入在我们的
Springwood application you saw that
您看到的Springwood应用程序
there's nothing special about this this
这个没什么特别的
is just a so-called fat jar I can deploy
就是我可以部署的所谓的胖子罐
it to climb finder here to any other or
它可以将finder爬到这里
two pivotal you know the pivotal
两个关键你知道关键
kubernetes service PCAST we can deploy
我们可以部署的kubernetes服务PCAST
it to that I mean whatever you want you
意思是说你想要什么
can deploy these apps you know into an
可以将您知道的这些应用程序部署到
until cloud just like you would any
直到像你一样云
other spring boon application and the
其他 Spring 优惠申请和
Kafka stream support here is using Kafka
Kafka流支持在这里使用Kafka
as the store and so that's
作为商店，所以
really all the magic is happening and
真的所有魔术都在发生，
you do have to be since you are dealing
你一定是因为你在交易
with a store and be the sensor is
与一家商店，并成为传感器
sterilization involved you'll see that
涉及灭菌，您会看到
that's kind of front and center and a
那是前面和中心，
lot of the stuff that we had to do here
我们在这里要做的很多事情
anyway you see the word Saturday that's
无论如何，您会看到“星期六”这个词
that's the surfacing of something that
那是一些东西的表面
is related to the fact that you're
与以下事实有关：
persisting data remember ultimately
持久数据最终记住
Kafka doesn't care is just it just sees
卡夫卡不在乎，只是看到
a bunch of bytes it doesn't care about
一堆无关紧要的字节
what the contents of those bytes are
这些字节的内容是什么
necessarily and then finally we um
一定然后最后我们
rather going on further we saw that you
宁愿继续，我们看到你
can do some you know very very
可以做一些非常非常了解的事情
interesting kind of routing with spring
用Spring进行有趣的路由
cloud stream so here I've got an input K
云流，所以在这里我有一个输入K
stream of string to page view event and
字符串到页面查看事件的流，以及
then I say it was a processor so I
然后我说这是一个处理器，所以我
created a K stream of string too long I
创建的K字符串流太长了
used just one value here but there's no
在这里只使用了一个值，但是没有
reason that I I couldn't for example
我不能举例的原因
send this to multiple topics actually so
实际发送给多个主题
you can the send two is actually an
您可以发送两个实际上是
array so for one so I could send this
数组，所以我可以发送这个
data to multiple to multiple
数据到多对多
destinations to multiple topics and you
多个主题的目的地，您
know this is great if you're doing event
知道这很棒，如果您正在参加活动
sourcing as well I can actually say okay
采购以及我实际上可以说很好
this is the the state of the system but
这是系统的状态，但是
I want other people are interested in
我希望其他人对此感兴趣
updating themselves based on that state
根据状态更新自己
to be aware of it for example so you can
例如知道它，这样您就可以
do interesting things there we looked at
在那儿做一些有趣的事情
the possibility for joining data which i
加入数据的可能性
think is one of the most you know
认为是你所知道的最多的之一
powerful opportunities that you have
您拥有的强大机会
here with Kafka streams as they believe
他们相信，这里有卡夫卡溪流
to take two different sets of data and
接受两组不同的数据
to merge them real time as you're
实时合并它们
processing and to arrive at synthesized
处理并合成
data we also looked at windowing which
数据我们还看了窗口
is another really amazing feature that
是另一个非常神奇的功能
you can do here in Kafka streams and
您可以在卡夫卡溪流中进行
that state is kept somewhere it's kept
状态被保存在某个地方
in the in the broker and so if you
在经纪人中，如果您
compare this to you know this looks very
比较一下，你知道这看起来非常
familiar to the spring code stream
熟悉Spring代码流
support for reactor right so you get
支持反应堆，这样您就可以
publishers and so on but that's state
出版商等等，但这是状态
for a reactor is it's in memory it's in
因为反应堆是在内存中
the java code it's in the java process
它在Java进程中的Java代码
so if you want to have if you have any
所以如果你想拥有的话
state that needs to be replicated across
需要在其中复制的状态
nodes there's no way to do that Kafka
节点没有办法做卡夫卡
streams give you the ability to scale
流使您能够扩展
this across as many nodes as you want
跨任意数量的节点
and still get a consistent you know
并仍然保持一致
picture of all what's being processed
所有正在处理的图片
what hasn't and so on so all of that
没有的东西等等
state management is done for you we
状态管理已为您完成
looked at a tables like I said K tables
看着一张桌子，就像我说的K桌子
are different slightly different beasts
是不同的略有不同的野兽
but there is a duality it's right
但有双重性是对的
for a case dream to become at a table
让一个梦想成真
and for a key table to become a case
并让关键表成为案例
stream and you can see that here right
流，你可以在这里看到
they've got a key table becoming a
他们有一个关键表成为
stream and so on visa versa and then we
流等等，反之亦然，然后我们
looked at the state store right the
看着国家商店的权利
state store I just used one of those
国营商店，我只是用其中之一
examples here but the the table you know
这里的例子，但你知道的表
that we were creating results in state
我们正在创造状态
being written somewhere and that state
被写在某个地方
is interrogate able and so you can
具有审讯能力，因此您可以
actually look at that state like a
实际上看那个状态就像一个
database it becomes a key value store
数据库，它成为键值存储
that's really really powerful so now I
那真的很强大，所以现在我
can actually have a you know as long as
其实只要你知道
I can coerce all of my different
我可以强迫我所有的不同
disparate sets of data into a key table
分散的数据集到一个关键表中
or a case stream then I can process it
或案例流，然后我可以处理它
here in this code very simply and
在这段代码中非常简单，
massage it and so on and I can do so
按摩等等，我可以这样做
independent of scale right I mean I can
与规模无关，我是说我可以
scale to like we said in the case of
扩展到我们所说的情况
Netflix billions of events per day and
Netflix每天发生数十亿个事件，并且
so still be the same fundamental
所以仍然是相同的基础
mechanism now when we use sprinkled
现在，当我们使用洒水机制
streams and kafka streams we get a lot
流和kafka流，我们得到了很多
of benefits we're building of course on
我们当然会建立的好处
top of the spring boot
spring boot 的顶部
auto-configuration
自动配置
like so remember we have the spring for
就像这样，记得我们有 Spring
Kafka project that's the basis for the
卡夫卡项目是
all the auto-configuration here that's
这里所有的自动配置
the thing that gives you the auto
给你自动的东西
configuration for your Kafka template
Kafka模板的配置
for example and your consumers and so on
例如和您的消费者等等
so in in you know I can say spring that
所以在你知道我可以说 Spring
Kafka bootstraps servers equals full bar
卡夫卡引导服务器等于满吧
I can point it to the producer
我可以指向制作人
information client ID the seer lasers
信息客户ID观察者激光器
all that stuff I can specify at this
我可以在此指定的所有内容
basis most basic of levels and this is
基础最基本的水平，这是
the kind of stuff that you'd have to
你必须要的那种东西
remember to set when you use the
记得在使用时设定
confluent cloud hosted a Kafka for
融合云托管了一个Kafka
example right that that's in spring boot
在 spring boot 中的示例示例权
and that builds on the spring for Kafka
而这正是卡夫卡 Spring 的来临
project spring for Apache Kafka project
Apache Kafka项目的项目 Spring
then we have spring cloud we had spring
然后我们有 Spring 的云，我们有了 Spring
irrigation and Kafka social innovation
灌溉与卡夫卡社会创新
and Kafka there's a adapters in banner
和卡夫卡在横幅上有一个适配器
nap and adapters for for spring
午睡和Spring 适配器
integration and then we have the spring
整合，然后我们有了 Spring
cloud stream Kafka support which is what
云流卡夫卡的支持是什么
we're looking at here and then we have
我们在这里看，然后有
the spring cloud stream Kafka stream
Spring Cloud Stream 卡夫卡流
support so it can be a little dizzying
支持，所以可能有点头晕
but you can see here that at the highest
但您可以在这里看到最高的
level using the most abstract of those
最抽象的那些水平
api's the spring code stream Kafka
api是 Spring 代码流Kafka
streams support we get a lot of power
流支持我们获得了巨大的力量
and really really can really convenient
真的真的很方便
to processing technology
加工技术
all right we we also looked ever so
好吧，我们看上去也是如此
briefly at at the the topology we talked
简要介绍了我们讨论的拓扑
about the topology of a Kafka system but
关于Kafka系统的拓扑，但是
it's it's really important to understand
了解它真的很重要
that we're taking advantage of the fact
我们利用了事实
that there are partitions here and that
这里有分区
there are groups so you saw at one point
有小组，所以你在一眼看到
I had to use a group and that allows
我不得不使用一个小组，这允许
multiple consumers to to have to be
必须有多个消费者
listeners to other streams you know
收听您知道的其他流的听众
that's that's an important part so
那是很重要的部分
you're going to find when you get when
你会发现什么时候得到的
you dive into Kafka
你潜入卡夫卡
that you need to really care about
你需要真正关心的
partitions and you need to care about
分区，您需要关心
the consumer right there there is the
那里的消费者
concept of the producer in the consumer
消费者中生产者的概念
and the consumer ultimately contains the
并且消费者最终包含了
it knows about the offset it knows about
它知道它所知道的偏移量
how many records into that sequential
那个顺序有多少条记录
log of records it has read and it can
它已读取的记录日志，它可以
control that it can it can seek to the
控制它可以寻求的
latest offset and just start from the
最新的偏移量，只需从
new ones I start processing and draining
新的我开始处理并耗尽
the queue from the new ones or can go
来自新队列的队列，或者可以去
back to the very first one and replay
回到第一个并重播
every single existing message and Kafka
每个现有的消息和卡夫卡
itself is there is a log
本身有一个日志
so he gets min to store data on file
这样他就可以将数据存储在文件中
system like I said it can be 10
我说的系统可以是10
kilobytes or 10 terabytes it doesn't
千字节或10 TB
matter right so you have a lot of a lot
没关系，所以你有很多
of power here that makes it a make it a
的力量使它成为一个
very very reliable system for large
非常非常可靠的大型系统
amounts of data especially large amounts
大量的数据，特别是大量
of data that needs to be processed in
需要处理的数据
real time and of course if you're doing
实时，当然，如果您在做
it in terms of a spring boot it couldn't
就 spring boot 而言，它不能
get simpler alright my friends with that
让我的朋友们变得更简单
thank you so very much and we'll see you
非常感谢您，我们将再见
next time
下次
you
您